Guide to the Toni Beauchamp Papers
University of Houston Libraries
Toni Beauchamp Papers
1985-2008
2000-2008
02/2014-001
Beauchamp, Toni, 1945-2012
45.00 linear feet
Special Collections, University of Houston Libraries
This collection is housed in 45 boxes and organized into 12 series entitled: Buffalo Bayou Partnership, Market Square Park Project, Art Lies (the magazine), good (the book), Blaffer Gallery, Friends of Integrative Medicine, Uncommon Cents, News clippings, photographs, A/V Materials, and Ephemera/Index Cards. Materials within this collection have been arranged topically and therein in chronological order.
Biographical Information:
Toni Beauchamp was born in Houston Texas on September 11, 1945 to Margaret Brown and Raymond Gin. Due to racial tensions and pressures placed on her parents, which resulted in their divorce, Toni was reared until school age by her nurturing maternal grandmother, Minnie Bell Caddell Brown. This experience fueled her desire to bridge the racial gap in later years. Toni's mother eventually married John Nobler, and Toni soon gained a half sister, Carolyn.
While attending Lamar High School in 1961, Toni met her future husband and soul mate Jeff, who was then a student at UT Austin. Toni and Jeff were married in 1963 and would spend the next 48 years together working alongside each other in various ventures. Toni played a major role to the success of their first company, Intermat, which they sold in 1997.
Toni’s love for the arts prompted her to pursue a career in Art History. As a result, she earned her BA from the University of Houston and her MA from The University of Texas at Austin. She firmly believed in the transformative power of public art, and her 1983 Master's thesis on James Johnson Sweeney and the Museum of Fine Arts, Houston was a groundbreaking work of art history scholarship. The thesis recounted the life of the renowned museum curator and director, not only as a biographical narrative but also as an exploration of the city's art institutions and the development of the local art world. This publication generated many of the concepts that Toni would explore in later publications.
Her deep passions for all things art and her immense contributions to the art and civic worlds enabled her to affect change through her endless hours of service on boards and advisory committees. Toni will forever be remembered and beloved for her ability to use the power of art to transform the surrounding community. After a courageous battle with ovarian cancer, she passed away on March 9, 2012. She is survived by her husband Jeffery O. Beauchamp, her mother Margaret Brown, and her father Raymond Tong Gin.
Access Terms
This Collection is indexed under the following controlled access subject terms.
Corporate Name:
Buffalo Bayou Partnership; Cultural Arts Council Houston/Harris County; DiverseWorks
Genre/Form of Material:
Administrative records; Clippings (information artifacts); Correspondence; Photographs
Geographic Name:
Market Square Park (Houston, Tex.)
Topical Term:
Arts -- Texas -- Houston
Accruals:
Additional materials were acquired in 2014 as part of a donation by Jeff Beauchamp
Conditions Governing Access:
Open for research
Acquisition Information
Information of acquisition method not available.
Related Materials:
DiverseWorks Archival Records (http://archon.lib.uh.edu/index.php?p=collections/controlcard&id=599)
UH Creative Writing Program Records (http://archon.lib.uh.edu/index.php?p=collections/controlcard&id=594)
Scope and Contents
This collection is housed in 45 boxes and organized into 12 series entitled: Buffalo Bayou Partnership, Market Square Park Project, Art Lies (the magazine), good (the book), Blaffer Gallery, Friends of Integrative Medicine, Uncommon Cents, News clippings, photographs, A/V Materials, and Ephemera/Index Cards. Materials within this collection have been arranged topically and therein in chronological order.
Detailed List of Contents
- Master Planning Process, Buffalo Bayou Partnership, id165859
  Scope and Contents
  This series documents one of the major projects in which Toni Beauchamp was involved in a leadership role. It contains well-documented information that gives an account of the various roles and projects executed by Toni Beauchamp and others in developing the Buffalo Bayou Master Plan for Buffalo Bayou Park (BBP). It is further broken down into various subseries that detail history, correspondence, board of director, professional consultation/development, financials, networking/publicity, memoranda, projects, and other information as it relates to BBP.
  - History, id165860
    - Brief History, 2002; id165877 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Administrative Structure, 2002; id165878 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Goals, 2001-2003; id165879 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Master Plan, 2001-2002; id165880 (Box 1, Folder 4-5)
    - Strategic Planning Committee, 1995-1999; id165882 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Governance, 1999-2002; id165883 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Development, 1993-2003; id165884 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Pilot, Related Case Studies, and Research, id165861
    - Allen’s Landing Projects, 2000-2002; id165886 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Metro Project, 2002; id165887 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Land Conservancy Project, 2002; id165888 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Land Acquisition Project, 2002; id165889 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Environmental Reference; Heat Island Project, 2000-2002; id165890 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Parks and Recreation Project, 1999-2005; id165891 (Box 1, Folder 14-15)
    - Water Research Institute of Blue Hill Project, 1999; id165893 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Water Front Center Consulting Project, 1999; id165894 (Box 1, Folder 17-18)
    - Blue Gold Global Water Crisis Project, 1999; id165896 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Sabine Bagby Project, 2002; id165897 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - East End Bayou Project, 2002; id165898 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Houston Port Authority Project, 2001-2002; id165899 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Whitney Museum Project, 2002-2005; id165900 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Public Art Funding Project, 2001-2006; id165901 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Urban Planning Reference Project, 2001-2002; id165902 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - FotoFest, 2003-2004; id165903 (Box 1, Folder 26-27)
    - Blueprint Houston Final Report, 2003; id165905 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Design Centers, 2002; id165906 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Board of Directors, id165862
    - Orientation Materials, 1998-1999; id165908 (Box 2, Folder 1-2)
    - Meeting Packets, 1998-2002; id165910 (Box 2, Folder 3-6)
    - Meetings, 2000; id165914 (Box 2, Folder 7-9)
    - Meetings, 2002-2003; id165915 (Box 2, Folder 10-11)
    - Annual BBP Meetings, 2003-2004; id165916 (Box 2, Folder 12-13)
    - Executive Committee Meeting, 2000-2003; id165917 (Box 2, Folder 14-15)
    - Retreat, 2000-2002; id165918 (Box 2, Folder 16-17)
  - Memorandums, id165863
    - Guy Hagstette, 2001; id165920 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Alan Grathus, 2001; id165921 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Ranjan Nambiar, 2001; id165922 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Planning Team, 2001; id165923 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Anne Olson, 1999-2002; id165924 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Toni Beauchamp Personal Files, id165864
    - Member Biographies, 1997-2003; id165926 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Buffalo Bayou Partnership Meeting Notes, 1999; id165928 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Committee Retreat Notes, undated; id165929 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Various, undated; id165930 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Surveys, id165865
    - Houston Downtown Management District Surveys, 1999; id165932 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Professional Consultants, id165866
    - Leadership Coaching, 1994-2002; id165934 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Planners and Landscape Architects, 2000; id165935 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Thompson Design Group (TDG), undated; id165936 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Financials, id165867
    - Proposed Budget, 2001-2003; id165938 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Annual Report, 2006; id165939 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - BBP Finances and Expenses, 2000-2002; id165940 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Funding, 1999-2002; id165941 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Insurance, 2002; id165942 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Independent Auditor’s Report, 2002; id165943 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Sunset Coffee Building Financing Package, 2003; id165944 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Committees, id165868
    - Steering, 2001-2002; id165946 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Nominating, 2002; id165947 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Task Force, 2002; id165948 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Downtown Council of Chairs, 2002; id165949 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Strategic Planning, 1999-2000; id165950 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Publications, id165869
    - Newsletter, 1998-2005; id165952 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Downtown District Publication, 2000-2001; id165953 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Media Coverage, 2002-2003; id165954 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Artist Opportunity and Submittals Booklet, 2003; id165955 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Watershed, 2003-2005; id165956 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Beacon Free Press, 2002-2003; id165957 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Various, 1998-2005; id165958 (Box 3, Folder 26-27)
  - Special Events, id165870
    - Buffalo Bayou Regatta, 2003; id165961 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Houston Can you Imagine, 2002; id165962 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Urban Land Institute, 2001; id165963 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Quality of Life, 2001; id165964 (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - Public Art Presentation, 2003; id165965 (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - Various, 2001-2004; id165966 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Local Government, id165871
    - Harris County, 2002; id165968 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - Heritage, undated; id165969 (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - City of Houston, 2000-2003; id165970 (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - Contacts Information, 2000-2003; id165971 (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - Skimmer Boat, 2002; id165972 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Correspondence, id165872
    - Development Corp, 2002; id165975 (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - Aaron Tuley, 2001-2002; id165976 (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - Sarah Peterson, 2002; id165977 (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - Susanne Devich, 2001-2002; id165978 (Box 3, Folder 42)
    - Anne Olson, 2001-2002; id165979 (Box 3, Folder 43)
    - Buffalo Bayou Board Meetings, 2001-2003; id165980 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Toni relating to Buffalo Bayou, 2002-2005; id165981 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Cultural Arts Council of Houston/Harris County (CACHH) affiliated with BBP, 2003; id165982 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Various, 2003-2004; id165983 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Networking, id165873
    - Various Invitations and Contacts, undated; id165985 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Maps, id165874
    - Various Media Maps and Designs, 2002; id165987 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Posters, id165875
    - Poster Presentation, undated; id165989 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - International Water Front Center, id169603
    - Washington, D.C., 2002; id169604 (Folder 33)
    - Correspondence–Breen and Rigby Book Pro, 2002-2003; id169605 (Folder 34)
- Market Square Park Project, A Project of DiverseWorks, id165990
  This series, represnting another major project in which Toni Beauchamp was involved in a leadership role, contains detailed and documented information that gives an account of the various roles and works that Toni and others executed in relation to the Market Square Park Project (MSPP). The documents highlight the development and progression of the project. This series is further sub-divided into subseries that include history, projects, correspondence, financials, funding, board of directors, professional consultant, and printed materials related to MSPP.
  - History, id165991
    - Overview, 1985-1992; id166007 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Redevelopment, undated; id166008 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Renovation, 2008; id166009 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Articles of Incorporation (By-Laws), 1988-1990; id166010 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Slide Presentation, 1987-1990; id166011 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Updates / Basic Information, 1987-1990; id166012 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Summary of MSPP, 1991-1992; id166013 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - 501(c)(3) Documents, 1987-1993; id166014 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Landscape and Architectural Plans, 2008; id166015 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Conservatorship, undated; id166016 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Maintenance, 1987-1995; id166017 (Box 4, Folder 18-19)
    - Park Maintenance Resource, 1990-1994; id166019 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Project Management, 1987-1992; id166020 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Archive Notebook, undated; id166021 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Archive Notebook, undated; id166022 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Partners and Affiliates of MSPP, id165992
    - Downtown Houston Vision and Planning, 1986-1992; id166024 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Artist Information, undated; id166025 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Artwork Distribution; Two Top Donors, 1991-1993; id166026 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Business Volunteers for the Arts, undated; id166027 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Project Partners, 1987-1989; id166028 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Clock Tower Information, 1982-1988; id166029 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Junior League Involvement in MSPP, 1987-1988; id166030 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - MacArthur Park Public Art Program (Booklet), 1985; id166031 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Market Square Historic District, 1993; id166032 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Metro Elevated Rail, 1990; id166033 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - City of Houston, 1991-1995; id166034 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Metropolitan Detention Center, 1994; id166035 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, id165993
    - Morgan Hill, 1991; id166037 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Proposals and Related Correspondence, 1988-1992; id166038 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Various, 1989-1991; id166039 (Box 5, Folder 16-17)
  - Printed Materials, id165994
    - IRS, undated; id166041 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Press Releases, 1989-1992; id166042 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Site Plans and Maps, 1987; id166043 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Networking, id165995
    - Letterhead, 1988-1990; id166045 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Various Invitations, undated; id166046 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Donors, id165996
    - Edward Allen, 1988; id166049 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Jeff and Toni Beauchamp, 1992; id166050 (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Bill Hill, 1991; id166051 (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - Brown Foundation Grant, 1988-1992; id166052 (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Cooper Industries, 1988-1991; id166053 (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Cockrell Foundation, 1989; id166054 (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Enron Foundations, 1988-1992; id166055 (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - James Elkins III, 1988-1991; id166056 (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Romelia Favrot, 1991; id166057 (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - Fondren Foundation, 1989; id166058 (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - Guardian Savings, 1989-1991; id166059 (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - James Hayden, 1992; id166060 (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - Hamman Foundation, 1989; id166061 (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - Houston Park Board, 1988-1991; id166062 (Box 5, Folder 36)
    - KRTS FM 92.1 Foundation, 1991; id166063 (Box 5, Folder 37)
    - Kilroy Foundation, 1991; id166064 (Box 5, Folder 38)
    - Kenneth Dale Owen, 1990; id166065 (Box 5, Folder 39)
    - Smith Foundation, 1991; id166066 (Box 5, Folder 40)
    - Shell Oil Company, 1987-1991; id166067 (Box 5, Folder 41)
    - Scurlock Foundation, 1991; id166068 (Box 5, Folder 42)
    - Andy Warhol Foundation, 1991-1993; id166069 (Box 5, Folder 43)
    - Wortham Grant, 1987-1991; id166070 (Box 5, Folder 44)
    - A – C Donors, 1990-1991; id166071 (Box 5, Folder 45)
    - D – G Donors, 1990-1991; id166072 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - H – J Donors, 1990-1991; id166073 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - L – M Donors, 1990-1992; id166074 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - N – R Donors, 1990-1991; id166075 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - S Donors, 1990-1991; id166076 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - T Donors, 1990-1991; id166077 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - V – Z Donors, 1990-1991; id166078 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Park Donors and Copy of Text from Donor Column, 1991-1992; id166079 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Contribution Request, 1989-1990; id166080 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Corporate Contributions, 1991; id166081 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - In Kind Contributions, 1988-1990; id166082 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Recognition Options, 1990; id166083 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Foundation Turn Downs, 1989-1991; id166084 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Foundations in Progress, 1991-1992; id166085 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Pledge Forms, 1991; id166086 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Donor Lists, 1989-1991; id166087 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Fund Raising, 1988-1990; id166088 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Income Pledges / Continuing Donations, 1989-1991; id166089 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Income– Brick Donations, 1990; id166090 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Business Art Fund Houston Texas, 1985-1986; id166091 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Anthony Foundation, 1984-1985; id166092 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - MSPP Funding Status, 1990-1993; id166093 (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Herzstein Foundation, 1992; id166094 (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Various, 1990-1993; id166095 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Financials, id165997
    - Invoices – Accounts Receivable, 1990-1993; id166098 (Box 6, Folder 25-27)
    - Invoices – Accounts Receivable, 1990-1993; id166099 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - United Savings Deposits Information, 1990-1993; id166100 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Northern Trust Bank Account, 2003-2009; id166101 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Texas Commerce Bank, 1988-1994; id166102 (Box 7, Folder 4-6)
    - River Oaks Bank Checkbooks, id166105 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Texas Commerce Bank, 1988-1994; id166106 (Box 7, Folder 8-9)
    - River Oaks Bank Checkbook, id166108 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Floppy Disc, undated; id166109 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Tax, 1989-2000; id166110 (Box 7, Folder 12-13)
    - Reconciliations, 1989; id166112 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Budget, 1988-1992; id166113 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Interest – Income, 1990-1991; id166114 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - VSAT Money Desk– CD Investment, 1990-1991; id166115 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Adjusted Trial Balance, 1991-1992; id166116 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Cash Flow, 1992-1993; id166117 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Financial Statements, 1989-1990; id166118 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Ledger, undated; id166119 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Brick Sales and Reports, 1990-1991; id166120 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Invoices and Payments, 1991-1993; id166121 (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Financial Records, 1991-1992; id166122 (Box 7, Folder 24-25)
    - Kenneth H. Thorn – Treasury Reports, 1990-1991; id166124 (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - Check Registers / Transaction Reports, 1988-1991; id166125 (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - Treasury Report, 1989-1992; id166126 (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - Treasury Report, 1989-1992; id166128 (Box 8, Folder 1-2)
    - Maintenance Endowment, 1992-2007; id166130 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - CD Investment / CD Account, 1989-1992; id166131 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Financial History, 1987-1991; id166132 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Various, undated; id166133 (Box 8, Folder 6-9)
    - Records Storage, 1988-1991; id166134 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Committees/Subcommittees, id165998
    - Foundation, 1987-1992; id166136 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Research, 1987-1989; id166137 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Education, 1987; id166138 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Corporate, 1987-1988; id166139 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Documentation, 1987; id166140 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Steering Committee Meeting Minutes and Agendas, 1987-1988; id166141 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Steering Committee Rosters, 1987-1992; id166142 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Steering Committee Correspondence, 1986-1989; id166143 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Steering Committee General Notes, 1987-1989; id166144 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Special Events/Programs, id165999
    - A Guide to Houston Cultural Activities for the Young: Junior League of Houston Inc., undated; id166146 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Texas Historical Commission Section 106, 1991; id166147 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Dedication of Landmark Park, 1991-1992; id166148 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Annual Awards, 1994; id166149 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Historic District, 1991-1992; id166150 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Leadership Houston Cultural Diversity Program, 1986; id166151 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - TAPS Design Excellence Award Nomination, 1992-1994; id166152 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Ground-Breaking Ceremony General, 1990-1992; id166156 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Ground-Breaking Ceremony Press Kit, 1990-1991; id166157 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Ground-Breaking Ceremony Invitation List, 1990-1991; id166158 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - International Sculpture Symposium, 1989-2008; id166160 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - International Sculpture Gala, 2000; id166161 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - International Sculpture Conference, 2000; id169607 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Board of Directors, id166000
    - Monthly Meetings, 1990; id166165 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Meeting Minutes, 1989-1991; id166166 (Box 9, Folder 15-20)
    - Notebooks, undated; id166167 (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - Notebooks, undated; id166168 (Box 10, Folder 1-2)
    - Meeting Notes After Incorporation, 1987-1990; id166169 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Market Square Council Notes, 1987-1988; id166170 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Meeting Notes, 1991-1992; id166171 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Record File, 1987-1990; id166172 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Council– Correspondence Notes, 1987-1988; id166173 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Toni Beauchamp Personal File, undated; id166174 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Various, 1994; id166175 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Professional Consultant, id166001
    - Public Relations Firm– Joe Bacon, 1990-1991; id166177 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Gilbane Building Contract and Timeline, 1991; id166178 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Legal Assistant, 1988-1989; id166179 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Contract Artwork, 1990; id166180 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Public Relations Firm– Rivers Smith Baldwin Carlsberg, 1990; id166181 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Lauren Griffith Association, undated; id166182 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Gilbane Contract (TCB), 1991; id166183 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Insurance, id166002
    - Policies and Forms, 1990-1991; id166185 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Federal Agencies, id166003
    - National Endowment for the Arts, 1987-1992; id166187 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - DiverseWorks, id166004
    - History, id166188
      - Bylaws / Board members, 1986-1995; id166196 (Box 10, Folder 19)
      - Statement of purpose, id166197 (Box 10, Folder 20)
      - Long range plan, 1991; id166198 (Box 10, Folder 21)
      - General Info, 1990; id166199 (Box 10, Folder 22)
      - Administration, 1989; id166200 (Box 10, Folder 23)
      - Development, 1991-1993; id166201 (Box 10, Folder 24)
      - Documents, 1992-1994; id166202 (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - Board of Directors, id166189
      - Board Meetings, 1980-1995; id166205 (Box 10, Folder 26)
      - Meeting Packets, 1991-1992; id166206 (Box 10, Folder 27-28)
      - Meeting Packets, 1992-1993; id166207 (Box 10, Folder 29)
      - Meeting Packets, 1995-1996; id166208 (Box 11, Folder 1)
      - Co-directors, 1991-1993; id166209 (Box 11, Folder 2)
      - Retreat, 1990-1996; id166210 (Box 11, Folder 3)
      - Executive Committee Meeting, 1995; id166211 (Box 11, Folder 4)
      - Board of Directors Packets, 1995; id166212 (Box 11, Folder 5-6)
      - Executive Director Search, 1995; id166213 (Box 11, Folder 7-8)
      - Assistant Director Search, 1995; id166214 (Box 11, Folder 9)
      - Various, undated; id166215 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Committees, id166190
      - Search Committee, 1995; id166217 (Box 11, Folder 11)
      - Executive Committee, 1990-1993; id166218 (Box 11, Folder 12)
      - Planning, 1988-1991; id166219 (Box 11, Folder 13)
      - Sponsorship, 1993; id166220 (Box 11, Folder 14)
      - Foundation, 1993; id166221 (Box 11, Folder 15)
      - Nominating, 1993-1996; id166222 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Funding, id166191
      - Fundraising, 1996-1997; id166225 (Box 11, Folder 17-18)
      - Donors, 1996-1997; id166226 (Box 11, Folder 19)
      - Donor List, 1991; id166227 (Box 11, Folder 20)